export const quizData = [
  {
    question:
      'Q-1: What is the ancient civilization that revered cats as gods?',
    answers: ['Egyptian', 'Aztec ', 'Maya', 'Inca'],
    correct: 'Egyptian',
  },
  {
    question: 'Q-2: Which of the following is not a cat breed',
    answers: ['Siamese', 'Labrador', 'Persian', 'Bengal'],
    correct: 'Labrador',
  },
  {
    question:
      'Q-3: In which animated movie is a cat named "Puss in Boots" one of the main characters',
    answers: ['Shrek the third', 'Shrek 2', 'Shrek 1', 'Super Mario'],
    correct: 'Shrek 2',
  },
  {
    question: 'Q-4: Which of the following foods is not safe to feed to a cat?',
    answers: ['Raw fish', 'Cooked chicken', 'Chocolate', 'Milk'],
    correct: 'Chocolate',
  },
  {
    question: 'Q-5: What is a distinctive feature of Siamese cats?',
    answers: [
      'Long tail',
      'Intense blue eyes and a light-colored fur body',
      'Red eyes',
      'Small ears',
    ],
    correct: 'Intense blue eyes and a light-colored fur body',
  },
  {
    question: 'Q-6: On average, how many whiskers does a cat have?',
    answers: [
      '12 - 15 whiskers',
      '24 - 28 whiskers',
      '1 - 2 whiskers',
      'No whiskers',
    ],
    correct: '24 - 28 whiskers',
  },
  {
    question:
      'Q-7: What is the name of the largest cat ever recorded in history?',
    answers: ['Big foot', 'Kitkat', 'Titen', 'Hercules'],
    correct: 'Hercules',
  },
  {
    question:
      "Q-8: What is the name of the famous cat in Charles Perrault's tale that wears boots and a top hat?",
    answers: ['Puss in Boots', 'Garfield', 'Johny', 'Mark'],
    correct: 'Puss in Boots',
  },
  {
    question:
      'Q-9: What is the organ that allows cats to balance themselves when falling from a height?',
    answers: [
      'The tail',
      'The feets',
      'The inner ear or labyrinth',
      'The claws',
    ],
    correct: 'The inner ear or labyrinth',
  },
  {
    question: 'Q-10: Which of the following is not a common fur color in cats?',
    answers: ['Tabby', 'Marbled', 'Plaid', 'Calico'],
    correct: 'Plaid',
  },
];

export const gameData = {
  score: 0,
};
